This kind of propaganda has too many. No one believes it.
Too many what?
Too many. Too much. No one believes it.
Except a few Israelis.
We really do all that we can not to hurt the citizens.
To kill more than 70,000 civilians.
There are more than terrorists.
This is not fact. They're right.
Okay.
Really.
The fact is not decided by you.
The facts are decided by the international community.
It's not decided by your government.
Your government has no legitimacy and right to decide or defend what is fact.
My solution is that go to the UN, work with the UN,
and agree the two-state solution to establish the state of Palestine.
What do we need to do about the terror organization?
My answer is very clear.
Yeah.
Your military people should shoot the terrorists, not the children, not the women.
We shoot the children and the women.
And your lot of legitimacy to carry it out.
Any actions in that reason.
other reason.
And the other reason.